

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer (Java) with 6 Years' experience in Angular JS, Spring Boot, Spring microservices, Hibernate, JPA, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Java/J2EE, Rabbit MQ, Kendo UI, Jenkins and Maven.

Successful background in development of Real Time Trade Monitoring platform for Equity/Forex, loan cycle platform, and multiple 3-tier based applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2015 - Present ASSISTANT MANAGER

Edelweiss Financial Services, Mumbai.

Responsible for handling team and development of multiple applications for finance related businesses/FinTech requirements. Delivered applications for Stock market trading business and NBFC domain.

2014 – 2015 **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

Pratham Software Pvt. Ltd., Jaipur.

Responsible for designing and developing set of significant components in BPM application, Created workflows for credit document data capture and developed a web application for publishing workflow data.

2013 – 2014 JAVA DEVELOPER

Midnight Oxygen Pvt. Ltd., Jaipur.

Responsible for development of multiple web based applications.

EDUCATION

2010 – 2013 MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS

Suresh Gyan Vihar University, Jaipur.

GPA - 8.38/10

2007 – 2010 BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS

University of Rajasthan, Jaipur.

GPA - 67/100

8A- Winnie House, Kalina Market, MUMBAI- 400098 +91-98929 86762 or +9196727 92727 mohitarora.j2ee@gmail.com

AWARDS

WALKING THE EXTRA MILE - 2018

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING/

FRAMEWORK

JAVA/J2EE

ANGULAR JS

SPRING-BOOT

SPRING SECURITY/ CORE

PL/SQL

JPA/HIBERNATE MICROSERVICES

DATABASE/TOOLS

POSTGRESQL

MongoDB

MSSQL SERVER

ECLIPSE

MAVEN/JENKINS

JIRA/BITBUCKET

RABBITMQ

PROJECTS

QUBER – CORPORATE LENDING (SPRINGBOOT/JAVA-J2EE/POSTGRESQL/ANGULARJS)

ORION – TRADE MONITORING (SPRING/JAVA-J2EE/MONGODB)

SHARESPACE – SECURE SHARED
DATA MANAGEMENT TOOL
(SPRINGBOOT/SECLORE/ANGULARJS
/JAVA-J2EE)

CONNECT

LINKEDIN.COM/IN/MOHITARORALIVE
HTTPS://MOHITARORA.HEROKUAPP.COM/